devhood.com 2003-10-01

# Terms and Conditions of DevHood

| 

## DevHood Privacy Policy 

Your use of the DevHood Web site constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and consent to the terms herein. Please see the section labeled "Information We Collect and How We Use It" to learn more about our collection and use of user information. 

### Introduction 

DevHood is committed to safeguarding the privacy of visitors to our Web site and users of the other services available through our site (the "Service(s)"). We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you provide us remains private and is used only for the purposes set forth herein. 

This privacy policy details our commitment to protect your information and the limited manner in which we will use that information to provide and improve our provision of the Services. 

### Important Terms Used Throughout This Privacy Policy 

Throughout this privacy policy we use several specialized terms. "Personally Identifiable Information" is information that tells us specifically who you are, like your name, street address, email address, billing address, credit card number and expiration date. "User Information" means all Personally Identifiable Information and any other forms of information discussed in this privacy policy, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address of a user's computer. We use the term "aggregate" when we combine information from various persons or users. Information is said to be "anonymized" if it does not identify individual persons or entities or associate a particular person or entity with such information. 

### Information We Collect and How We Use It 

If you visit our site to browse. We will only collect and store the domain name and host from which a user accessed the Internet (e.g., aol.com), the IP address of the user's computer, the user's browser software and operating system, the date and time the user accesses the site and the Internet address of any Web site from which the user linked directly to our site or to which the user links after visiting our site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to sections of our sites, to determine from where our visitors linked and to where our visitors link from the sites and to help us make our sites more useful. For example, we organize and analyze IP addresses so that we can provide efficient service, enhance security, monitor appropriate usage and produce traffic volume statistics. This type of information is sometimes shared with third parties, such as when we aggregate and disclose site traffic information for marketing and commercial purposes. When we share such information with third parties we will require them to abide by the standards of this privacy policy. 

If you register or engage in a transaction while at our site. To make full use of our Services you will need to complete our registration process. We collect and store the Personally Identifiable Information you provide through this registration process, including your user ID and password, which we may elect to provide for you. If you engage in a transaction while logged on to our site, then we collect and store information about the transaction. If you send us communications, then we may collect such communications in a file specific to you. 

We use the information we collect from you as a registered user to build features that we hope will make the Services more attractive and easier for you to use. This may include better customer support and timely notice of new services. We may share User Information with our partners, affiliates and joint venturers that are committed to serving your need for the Services and improving your user experience, but will require such third parties to abide by the standards of this privacy policy. We may also share aggregate anonymized data relating to activity on the site and use of the Services, such as demographical and statistical information, for marketing, research and other purposes. Furthermore, we may need to disclose User Information to law enforcement or other government officials if appropriate for your protection or in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or our users to legal liability. 

### If You Do Not Wish to Disclose User Information 

If you do not want to provide us with certain User Information then you may opt out by not using the Service that provides us with such User Information. For example, if you do not want us to retain your name, then you may choose not to become a registered user. You will not be entitled to the benefits of registration, but you are still free to browse the site and to visit the parts of the site accessible to non-registrants. 

### Cookies 

Cookies are small text files that our site can send to your browser for storage on your hard drive. Cookies can make your use of our site easier by saving your status and preferences upon visits to our site. The cookies are refreshed every time you enter the site. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you may be able to change the settings to refuse cookies or to be alerted when cookies are being sent. We use cookies for two purposes: (1) to enable DevHood to customize information for certain segments of its customer base; and (2) in some instances, to associate you with your User Information. For example, through the use of cookies you may login automatically and thereby save you time. Although rejection of cookies will not interfere with your ability to interact with most of our site, you will need to accept cookies in order to login and use certain interactive Services on the site. 

### Control of Your Password 

Except as specifically permitted by this privacy policy or your User Agreement you may not disclose your DevHood password to any third parties nor share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your DevHood password you may lose control over your Personally Identifiable Information, and you will be responsible for any legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password or, if we provided your password, notify DevHood so that we may issue you a new password. 

### Removal or Correction of Personally Identifiable Information 

Upon your request, we may remove your Personally Identifiable Information from our database and correct any errors you identify in such information. If Personally Identifiable Information is removed you will lose access to the parts of the site for which you must provide such Personally Identifiable Information to gain access. After removal, we will only retain copies of such information as are necessary for us to comply with governmental orders, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, enforce any agreement you have entered into through our sites and as otherwise reasonably necessary. Any Personally Identifiable Information provided as a part of a transaction on the site represents a record of that business transaction that cannot be altered after the transaction is complete. 

### Third Parties 

This privacy policy only addresses the use and disclosure of User Information collected by DevHood. If you disclose information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of such information regardless of their affiliation or relationship with DevHood. Because DevHood does not control the privacy practices of third parties you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of those third parties. When you link to another Web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that Web site. We encourage you to ask questions and review the applicable privacy policy before you disclose your personal information to third parties. 

We do not try to control, and disclaim responsibility for, information provided by other users or third parties that is made available through our site. Such information may contain errors, intentional or otherwise, or may be offensive, inappropriate or inaccurate, and in some cases will be mislabeled or deceptively labeled. 

### Merger, Assets, Sales, etc. 

If DevHood or any of its lines of business is sold, pledged or disposed of as a going concern whether by merger, sale of assets, bankruptcy or otherwise, then the user database of DevHood could be sold as part of that transaction and all User Information accessed by such successor or purchaser. 

### How do I Contact DevHood 

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you can contact DevHood by email at [devhood@mit.edu](mailto:devhood@mit.edu) . 

### Miscellaneous 

DevHood may from time to time change this privacy policy with or without notice, so please check it regularly for any changes or updates. For future reference, DevHood will make a link to the current privacy policy available to you on your screen when you are on our Web site. Your use of the site constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and your assent to any modification thereto.  | 
| 

## DevHood Privacy Policy 

Your use of the DevHood Web site constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and consent to the terms herein. Please see the section labeled "Information We Collect and How We Use It" to learn more about our collection and use of user information. 

### Introduction 

DevHood is committed to safeguarding the privacy of visitors to our Web site and users of the other services available through our site (the "Service(s)"). We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you provide us remains private and is used only for the purposes set forth herein. 

This privacy policy details our commitment to protect your information and the limited manner in which we will use that information to provide and improve our provision of the Services. 

### Important Terms Used Throughout This Privacy Policy 

Throughout this privacy policy we use several specialized terms. "Personally Identifiable Information" is information that tells us specifically who you are, like your name, street address, email address, billing address, credit card number and expiration date. "User Information" means all Personally Identifiable Information and any other forms of information discussed in this privacy policy, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address of a user's computer. We use the term "aggregate" when we combine information from various persons or users. Information is said to be "anonymized" if it does not identify individual persons or entities or associate a particular person or entity with such information. 

### Information We Collect and How We Use It 

If you visit our site to browse. We will only collect and store the domain name and host from which a user accessed the Internet (e.g., aol.com), the IP address of the user's computer, the user's browser software and operating system, the date and time the user accesses the site and the Internet address of any Web site from which the user linked directly to our site or to which the user links after visiting our site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to sections of our sites, to determine from where our visitors linked and to where our visitors link from the sites and to help us make our sites more useful. For example, we organize and analyze IP addresses so that we can provide efficient service, enhance security, monitor appropriate usage and produce traffic volume statistics. This type of information is sometimes shared with third parties, such as when we aggregate and disclose site traffic information for marketing and commercial purposes. When we share such information with third parties we will require them to abide by the standards of this privacy policy. 

If you register or engage in a transaction while at our site. To make full use of our Services you will need to complete our registration process. We collect and store the Personally Identifiable Information you provide through this registration process, including your user ID and password, which we may elect to provide for you. If you engage in a transaction while logged on to our site, then we collect and store information about the transaction. If you send us communications, then we may collect such communications in a file specific to you. 

We use the information we collect from you as a registered user to build features that we hope will make the Services more attractive and easier for you to use. This may include better customer support and timely notice of new services. We may share User Information with our partners, affiliates and joint venturers that are committed to serving your need for the Services and improving your user experience, but will require such third parties to abide by the standards of this privacy policy. We may also share aggregate anonymized data relating to activity on the site and use of the Services, such as demographical and statistical information, for marketing, research and other purposes. Furthermore, we may need to disclose User Information to law enforcement or other government officials if appropriate for your protection or in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or our users to legal liability. 

### If You Do Not Wish to Disclose User Information 

If you do not want to provide us with certain User Information then you may opt out by not using the Service that provides us with such User Information. For example, if you do not want us to retain your name, then you may choose not to become a registered user. You will not be entitled to the benefits of registration, but you are still free to browse the site and to visit the parts of the site accessible to non-registrants. 

### Cookies 

Cookies are small text files that our site can send to your browser for storage on your hard drive. Cookies can make your use of our site easier by saving your status and preferences upon visits to our site. The cookies are refreshed every time you enter the site. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you may be able to change the settings to refuse cookies or to be alerted when cookies are being sent. We use cookies for two purposes: (1) to enable DevHood to customize information for certain segments of its customer base; and (2) in some instances, to associate you with your User Information. For example, through the use of cookies you may login automatically and thereby save you time. Although rejection of cookies will not interfere with your ability to interact with most of our site, you will need to accept cookies in order to login and use certain interactive Services on the site. 

### Control of Your Password 

Except as specifically permitted by this privacy policy or your User Agreement you may not disclose your DevHood password to any third parties nor share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your DevHood password you may lose control over your Personally Identifiable Information, and you will be responsible for any legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password or, if we provided your password, notify DevHood so that we may issue you a new password. 

### Removal or Correction of Personally Identifiable Information 

Upon your request, we may remove your Personally Identifiable Information from our database and correct any errors you identify in such information. If Personally Identifiable Information is removed you will lose access to the parts of the site for which you must provide such Personally Identifiable Information to gain access. After removal, we will only retain copies of such information as are necessary for us to comply with governmental orders, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, enforce any agreement you have entered into through our sites and as otherwise reasonably necessary. Any Personally Identifiable Information provided as a part of a transaction on the site represents a record of that business transaction that cannot be altered after the transaction is complete. 

### Third Parties 

This privacy policy only addresses the use and disclosure of User Information collected by DevHood. If you disclose information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of such information regardless of their affiliation or relationship with DevHood. Because DevHood does not control the privacy practices of third parties you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of those third parties. When you link to another Web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that Web site. We encourage you to ask questions and review the applicable privacy policy before you disclose your personal information to third parties. 

We do not try to control, and disclaim responsibility for, information provided by other users or third parties that is made available through our site. Such information may contain errors, intentional or otherwise, or may be offensive, inappropriate or inaccurate, and in some cases will be mislabeled or deceptively labeled. 

### Merger, Assets, Sales, etc. 

If DevHood or any of its lines of business is sold, pledged or disposed of as a going concern whether by merger, sale of assets, bankruptcy or otherwise, then the user database of DevHood could be sold as part of that transaction and all User Information accessed by such successor or purchaser. 

### How do I Contact DevHood 

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you can contact DevHood by email at [devhood@mit.edu](mailto:devhood@mit.edu) . 

### Miscellaneous 

DevHood may from time to time change this privacy policy with or without notice, so please check it regularly for any changes or updates. For future reference, DevHood will make a link to the current privacy policy available to you on your screen when you are on our Web site. Your use of the site constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and your assent to any modification thereto.  |
